GANESH K

STUDENT

I am a 2nd year college student at SRMIST, pursuing B.Tech in Computer Science and Engineering. I am skilled in web development languages and also am well experienced in programming. I am also learning Coding languages besides my working skills.

Contact

Phone

9384002566

Email

ganeshrajan2.00@gmail.com

Address

31,kasiappar street, East Tambaram.Chennai-600059.

Education

2009-2021

Class 1 -12

Alwin Memorial Public School

2021-Present

B Tech-CSE(Core)

SRM Institute of Science and Technology

Expertise

- Python
- SQL
- C/C++
- HTML
- CSS

Language

English

Tamil

Hindi

French

Experience

Q 2009 - 2022

AMPS I Indira Nagar, Selaiyur -600073

Student

School Life is the best time of our life as we make new friends, learn new things and build our career there. School time is the only time which we enjoy most, and when we enter college, we always miss our school life. School life teaches us lots of new things and prepares us to face all the challenges of life. I love my school life and really enjoy it. I have lots of friends, and all my teachers love me. I love my school and enjoy going there every day to meet my friends and learn new things.

2022 - Present

SRMIST | Potheri-600128

Student

College Life is one of the most remarkable and lovable times of an individual's life. Unlike School Life, College Life has a different experience, and a person needs to have this experience in his/her life. College Life exposes us to whole new experiences which we always dream of experiencing after our school life. Lucky are those who get the chance to enjoy their college life, as many people don't get this chance due to their circumstances or financial issues. For every person, College Life has a different meaning. While some people spend their college life partying with friends, others become more cautious about their careers and study hard. Whatever the way, every individual enjoys their college life and always wishes to relive that time once it is over.

Reference

Rajan Kumar

Student, SRMIST Phone: 8939414504

Email: ganraj2002@gmail.com